Vai, mi-era așa de somn la ultima oră!
Yuki, la ce te uiți?
Ți-am mai spus să nu vorbești cu mine.
Vor apărea zvonuri enervante.
Și ce dacă?
Suntem prieteni din copilărie,
deci cui îi pasă?
Poate ție nu-ți pasă de bărfe,
dar celorlalți da.
Chiar ți-a crescut părul, Yuki.
Pari anti-social când ai
un ochi acoperit astfel.
Hei.
Ai vrea să te tund la fel ca pe vremuri?
Yuhi, nu te-ai schimbat deloc.
Pentru mine, tu ești și mereu vei fi Yuki.
Iar asta nu se va schimba vreodată!
Sigur, îți voi accepta oferta.
Perfect. Te voi face să arăți grozav!
Mă întreb cum merg
lucrurile în „cealaltă lume”.
Ce?
Hei, ce se petrece?!
Ce e asta?
Nu se poate...
Eram în clasă acum câteva momente, nu?
Știam eu! Acest loc este...
Yuki?
Hei, ați auzit cumva ceva?
C-Ce e chestia aia?
Se filmează cumva un film?
Sunt controlați prin magie.
Hei, pare destul de real, nu?!
Se îndreaptă spre noi!
Toată lumea, fugiți! Repede!
Yuki!
Ce? Yuki?!
Stai, ce tocmai am făcut...
Nu avem timp de asta
acum. Haide, să fugim!
H-Hei, Yuki!
Yuki! Privește!
La atac!
Eliminați demonii!
Divizia de Magie, foc!
Ce se petrece?
Aceste războaie ar fi trebuit
să se sfârșească până acum.
Acea magie... E cumva un blestem?!
Această senzație... Nu e nicio
îndoială. Este cu siguranță...
Yuki?
Hei, voi!
Ce căutați aici?
Nu sunteți în siguranța
aici. Plecați imediat!
Cavalerii Regali vă vor
proteja. Haide, plecați!
B-Bine!
Bun. Să mergem!
Cavaleri Regali, pregătiți-vă de luptă!
Urmați-mă!
S-Sunt puternici!
Da, fără îndoială.
Bun, haide să mergem,
Yuhi! Poți alerga?
D-Da!
Episodul 1
Invocat pentru a doua oară într-o altă lume
Vă mulțumim că ați venit într-un moment critic cum este acesta, eroi străini!
Regatul Distinia
Regatul nostru, Distinia, e invadat de demoni.
La fel ca în războiul purtat acum cinci ani,
a group of heroes has rushed to
our aid from a foreign world!
Dacă asta nu e mâna destinului,
atunci nu știu ce e.
Ce vrea să spună prin „eroi”?
La ce se referă prin „mâna destinului”?
I'm sure you are all confused
by this sudden turn of events,
but the fact is that a hero who came to
us from a foreign world five years ago
ended the war raging across our world,
Eclaire, and brought peace.
Monumentul de
Comemorare a Păcii
That was five years ago, huh?
I know this alien world is confusing to you,
but please understand that we
cannot see this as a coincidence.
Could you please lend us aid?
Lend aid? I don't know how to fight.
But I don't want to get
thrown out of the castle...
If we have to do it, I guess
it's better to stay here...
Yeah, if we go outside and get attacked
again, we'll definitely be done for.
Thank you for your determination, everyone.
We have prepared rooms for you.
Please rest for today.
Ce se petrece?
Yuki...
Nu-ți face griji.
I won't let any danger come to you.
Bine.
Don't let your swing waver,
even unconsciously!
Make the proper form second nature!
Magic is a manifestation
of your mental image.
Try to create a solid image inside you.
Huh?
I-I did it!
Yuhi has talent.
Slacking off on your first day?
That's not very admirable.
Ack... Elka!
We're going to war.
Addressing your superior officer
like that is not permissible.
Sheesh, who cares how I address you?
Why don't you add "-sama" to your name,
if that's what you want?
Your calm composure in an alien
environment is commendable,
but your selfish attitude reminds
me of the hero from five years ago.
Capricious, egotistical, and uncaring
of how the women around him felt...
In any case, this world is more
dangerous than you might think.
Return to your training,
unless you want me to force you.
Sounds fun. I'd like to see you try.
I see. I guess a little pain
is needed as a lesson.
Th-This impact... Could it be...
Remember me now?
Se... Se...
Setsu-sama!
S-S-S-Setsu-sama! I-It's been such a long time!
I've waited for this moment,
to see you again, for so long!
Er, yeah. Long time no see.
How long are you gonna stay like that?
Oh! My apologies! Yes, the chair, right away!
No, I didn't ask for that...
Ah, the weight of Setsu-sama!
Oh, did you lose weight?
Yeah, this body is built differently
from the previous one.
You know, it's kind of creepy that you can tell.
I only feel pleasure from servitude
when providing it to you!
Oh, my master!
Her masochism has only accelerated
since the last time...
What are you doing?
Glein!
It's Setsu-sama! Setsu-sama is back!
Setsu-san? Wait, is that him?
I guess it has to be, given Elka's state...
Thea! Great news!
Listen—
Welcome back, Setsu.
It's good to see you again.
I knew you'd catch on quick, Thea.
Even with your new look,
I would never mistake
your magic power, Setsu.
I see. Magic is not my strong suit. I'm sorry.
I-I kinda sorta knew, too! I just wasn't sure!
Anyway...
I'm back, as promised.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Setsu.
I've been waiting for you.
I had no doubt you were alive!
Damn right I am!
I guess it's not a given, actually.
They could have died in battle
while I was gone from this world.
Is something wrong?
The war with the demons, right?
We have many questions
for you, too, Setsu-sama.
Let's go someplace else.
So, how did you return
to our world, Setsu-sama?
There's no doubt that you're Setsu-san,
but why do you look so different?
From our point of view, you simply
disappeared after that battle.
To be honest, I don't know for sure, either.
Toma!
Setsu!
What I know for sure is that
I was reborn in a different world while
keeping my memories and magic power,
then got summoned into this world again.
We don't know how you were summoned
to our world from a different world.
So, not to quote the princess,
but this doesn't seem like a coincidence.
The will of God is a mystery
to ordinary men like us.
Enough about me for now.
What happened to Toma after all that?
He could be behind this war, too, right?
Are those demons being controlled by a curse?
Yeah, that feeling in their
magic power... I'm certain.
It's a curse.
Toma's the only one who could
do something like that.
We searched for him, too,
like we searched for you, but...
We weren't able to find anything.
But seeing as Setsu is alive,
Toma could be, too...
Glein-sama!
Glein-sama, the king requires
your immediate presence.
Please come to the throne room.
Well, you heard him.
Yikes. Sounds like trouble.
It's not hard to imagine what's up.
I'll be off, then.
It's not easy being important.
That was supposed to be your job, you know.
As if I'd ever accept a stuffy job like that.
My plan was to travel around
this world after the war.
I love this peaceful scenery.
The peace that Setsu won for
us has to be maintained.
Yeah, you're right.
Toma, what are you thinking?
We should never have struck
peace with the demons!
Our kingdom will now declare
all-out war on them!
Please be patient, my king!
The emissary we sent to the demonic
continent has not sent back word yet!
We must first accurately
understand the situation.
It's the demons who've begun an
unprovoked invasion against us.
The new heroes being summoned at the same
time is proof that justice is on our side.
Hmph.
We never should have listened to the
hero's cheap words five years ago
and agreed to that peace charter.
That hero going missing feels to me
like God wants us to unify the world.
Yes! Success!
Good job, Yuhi.
Y-Yuki-kun?! You surprised me!
Don't sneak up on me like that!
I saw your other attempt, as well.
You seem to have a knack for magic.
You think so?
What's wrong?
This is practice to hurt someone, isn't it?
Well...
Why would anyone go to war?
Yuhi...
But if I really have a talent for magic,
I'll protect you, Yuki-kun.
Yuhi...
Yeah, just overthinking something
never changes anything.
There you are, Setsu-sama.
I was able to buy us some time
by saying the heroes need more training,
but all-out war seems
unavoidable at this point.
I'm sorry.
Oh, well.
Right, then. I guess I'll go out
and stop the war by myself again.
Setsu-sama?
War is stupid. It has to be stopped.
Especially if Toma is behind it.
Setsu...
Then we will follow you,
as your personal guard!
It would be great to fight
alongside you again.
Researching magic is fun,
but traveling together is more fun.
No. This time around, I'm going alone.
Given the situation,
you can't all leave this place.
Besides, if Toma really is behind this,
there needs to be enough of a
fighting force staying here, as well.
But...
If you're my personal guard,
you'll listen, right?
How can I turn down a request like that?
Setsu is cruel.
Okay. Now I have to go and get what I need.
Why are there so many people?
We're going to war. Everyone's preparing.
Elka, I'm going in. Glein, cover me.
Wait, Elka!
Let's do this peacefully!
Feels like going back to
our dungeon crawling days.
Yeah. Most of the time,
Elka would dive in head-first and...
Sorry!
Oh, no, old habits...
I said we should do this peacefully...
Well, as long as no one finds him.
You think they won't?
It's a matter of time.
It's open.
Good!
Huh?
Yuki-kun?
Yuhi, we're going without you!
Oh, sorry!
Ah, here it is.
Long time no see to you, too, Kuromaru!
What?!
Hey, are you all right?!
Guards! Lock down the gates!
Don't let them escape!
They must've found out.
I'll buy us some time within the castle.
I guess I have to help him.
Elka, follow Setsu. You'll get in our way.
Hey!
She's right and you know it. Come on.
Oh, Setsu-sama!
Please, don't be so forceful!
Good. Everything is ready.
We'll try to buy as much time
as possible until you return.
I'm counting on you.
Yuki-kun!
Wh-Why? Where are you going?!
Hanabashira-san...
No. It's all right, Elka.
To tell you the truth, this is actually the
second time I've been summoned to this world.
Second time?
So, to stop this war, I'm going
to go meet an old acquaintance.
If you're going somewhere,
I'm going with you!
I want to go with you!
I promise I'll be useful! So please, I...
No. It's too dangerous for you, Yuhi.
Besides, this is something I have to do.
Then that's all the more reason...
I'm going because I don't
want to put you in danger.
You understand, don't you?
Yuki-kun...
Yeah, you're a kind person.
Hey, close your eyes for a moment.
My eyes?
What for?
Just do it.
Like this?
Wind magic and fire magic? Nice!
I know, right?
I'll do my best to get strong,
so that I can protect you in this world, too!
Ow!
What was that for?!
If you can dodge that the next
time I see you, you pass the test.
All right, I'm off!
Right!
Invocat pentru a doua oară într-o altă lume
Data viitoare
Pornind pentru a doua oară într-o călătorie
Data viitoare: Pornind a
doua oară într-o călătorie.